You're leaving so early today.
You're awake.
I was trying
not to wake you up.
Xiaorou
took a long leave
for some reason.
So I have to
handle a lot of things.
When will you come back tonight?
Well,
I'm not sure.
The press conference is approaching,
and there are many things to deal with.
Go back to sleep.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
But the woman who painted these paintings
is the woman Mr. Zhou can never forget.
Su,
Mu,
Chen.
Impossible.
Su Muchen has been dead for a long time.
These paintings
were stored here by her.
When Mr. Zhou first joined the company,
he was short of money.
Su Muchen went to the studio
she went to the studio as an assistant
in secret.
Sometimes she used Purple Vine
as her pen name.
She asked me to sell the paintings to make a living.
A few years ago, I needed money,
so I sold the paintings to the gallery.
I didn't expect
Mr. Zhou bought them at once.
After that,
whenever I gave him a painting,
he would buy it immediately.
I guess
he also found the deep affection
in every stroke
of these paintings.
How do you know so much?
What's your relationship with Su Muchen?
Because I used to be
her best friend.
Even Mr. Zhou's entry into the company
was arranged by Su Muchen with my help.
In fact,
I'm the matchmaker
of you and Mr. Zhou.
Isn't it ironic?
Even if Annie buries the past deep,
it can't change the fact
that you, the daughter of the Lu family,
were once a mistress.
You've done a good job
over the years.
Now that it's come to this,
I'll take a long vacation
and leave Lucheng in the next few days.
I'll leave the resignation procedures
to you.
Oh,
by the way,
considering our years of friendship,
I'll tell you one last secret.
Do you really think
Jiang Li became Lu Xu's fiancée
just by coincidence?
Yan,
hasn't Lu Xu been home these days?
The young master hasn't come back
since the second day of the wedding.
When did Jiang Li
leave today?
Ms. Jiang left early this morning
with Mr. Ke
this morning.
Alright.
You can go now.
Okay.
Wait.
Mumu loves fish the most.
Why didn't she eat any?
The cook left a few bones
in the fish today.
I'm afraid he would choke,
so we replaced it with abalone porridge.
Once Annie dilutes your shares,
you'll have no bargaining chips.
You won't even be able to support Mumu.
Come on,
pour the wine.
Three sixes.
Drink more.
Four sixes.
Open.
Ah.
Look who's there.
Who's that?
What a buzzkill.
Who is she?
Get out of here.
What's wrong, Young Master Lu?
Who is she?
Get out.
Let's go.
Your engagement with Jiang Li
was just a show
for me to see.
Did Li Xiaorou tell you that?
I haven't seen her these days.
Lu Qianqian,
except for you,
I'm just flirting with others.
Aren't you afraid I'll tell Mother about this?
Between giving up a son-in-law
and keeping a son,
do you think
to keep a son?
You should know better than I do.
Besides,
you already know
that we are
not related by blood,
don't you?
You sent someone to spy on me in Singapore?
Jiang Li's report
is much more frequent than you know.
Did you tell Mom?
Whether she knows or not
depends on you.
Are you going to be the good girl of the Lu family,
or my accomplice?
You're not surprised at all.
You knew it all along.
Of course, I'm not surprised.
I knew it ten years ago.
To be honest,
I was so excited that I couldn't sleep all night.
Stop it.
Zhou Jian and I
will never get a divorce.
Sister.
Jingmo.
You've been back for years.
It's time to stop wandering
and take on responsibilities at the company.
Grandpa.
The world is full of challenges.
I need more experience.
Oh,
how many years can I
protect you?
When your uncle and aunt
take over the company,
you'll be
crying
but can't even find a grave.
Grandpa,
you'll live a long life.
Don't say such unlucky words.
Then,
how about you move back in?
That way, I can see you every day.
What do you say?
If I really moved back,
you'd be tired of me
in three days.
Hmph!
You little rascal!
Who's the grandpa here,
you or me?
You are, of course.
Well,
by the way,
what about Yao Ting from Hongshou Insurance?
She's been waiting for you for half a year.
You don't even have dinner with her.
Yao Ting
is pretty
and smart.
It would hurt her more
if I meet her and reject her.
Then...
Tell me,
what exactly are you looking for?
Grandpa,
you promised me freedom in love.
Even if I marry a beggar,
you won't interfere.
That's what you said,
but bring a beggar back then.
Ah?
Now,
there's not even a trace.
I'm looking forward to holding your child.
Tell me the truth.
Do you have a boyfriend or not?
Grandpa,
when I find one,
I'll tell you for sure.
Okay?
Hmph!
Nonsense!
I've been in business for a lifetime.
I can see through you.
Tell me.
Who's the girl?
Well.
The girl in Jingmo's heart
is beautiful,
smart,
and has
great skills.
Well.
Even your sister-in-law knows it.
Tell me,
who is the girl?
You're kidding.
It's the first time
you've come to talk about business
in all these years.
If it's not for a girl,
I can't think of any other reason.
Hey,
don't try to get away with it.
Tell me.
Grandpa,
she's engaged.
Don't ask.
So what?
A goalkeeper
can't stop a goal?
Your grandma
was taken by your grandpa
with his charm.
Tell me,
Who is she?
I'll help you.
Grandpa,
it's getting late.
I'll go first.
Take care of yourself.
Ah.
Remember to take your medicine.
You...
You want to run away again.
I'll see Jingmo off.
You brat,
if you don't bring a girl back next time,
don't come in.
No,
you must bring one back.
Did you hear that?
Ah,
that was the assistant of the Lu family,
just delivering a document on the way.
Oh,
why do you
even care about
my visitors now?
It seems that you've set up a new trap.
I wonder which piece you're aiming at this time.
Zhou Jian refuses to fall into the trap,
and Jiang Li was taken away by you halfway.
I can't just
sit and wait to die, can I?
You always like to borrow strength.
I believe you can
break the deadlock
without hurting the harmony.
You can stop here.
Miss Lu.
The child has been picked up by his aunt.
Which aunt?
The one who came with you last time.
She said you had something urgent today.
Who allowed you to let a stranger take my child?
She...
She said you asked her to come.
Ah?
Help!
Put me down!
Jump!
You're from the Lu family.
This height won't kill you.
Aunt, put me down.
I'm scared.
Jump down,
and I'll buy you a new model of a robot.
I don't want it.
I want my mom.
Move aside.
Mumu,
don't be afraid.
Come down.
I can catch you.
Come on.
It's okay.
Take him to the car.
Okay.
Jiang Li,
what do you want to do?
I'm teaching him how to survive.
Do you remember this scar on my hand?
When I was his age,
I was pushed by older kids in the orphanage
into a cement pipe in a derelict building.
Guess how I survived?
I bit my teeth
and crawled out of the three-meter deep pipe.
My mouth was full of blood.
The Lu family
will never abandon us.
You've met Lu Xu, haven't you?
The bite marks on his mouth are left by you.
You'd better think it through.
Do you want to continue to be a canary in the shelter
or teach this child
to walk.
After all, when the Lu family has finished with you,
this child can still continue to run by himself.